Amanda Landers, it is time. The Amanda Land Summit has arrived this weekend at the People's
Forum in New York City. Now, if you are not one of the members of the actual summit, you can still
participate in some of our awesome events. One, we have Cracking Up the System, Going Down on
Saturday morning, where we are combining comics, Davidson Boswell and Christina Brown with
organizers, Angelica Landon and Claudia de la Cruz, to talk about organizing. I know so many of y'all
are like, what's the solution? What can I do? Well, we're not only going to tell you about what you
can do, but we're going to do it funny because that's what we do at Smart, Funny and Black
Projections. In addition, that evening, we have a live taping of Views from Amanda Land, the first
ever. And my guests will be, I am Blakely. I don't know why some of you, my fellow marshmallow
are trying to argue with me in the comments about this fact. I used to get butthurt and defensive
when Black people would make generalizations about me because I'm white. But eventually,
I decided that I was going to choose not to be offended by it anymore because I realized that
people make assumptions based on aggregate data. Because you understand that despite a lot of men
being like, well, not all men, you can look to data and your own experiences. You don't think Black
people look to their own experiences and the aggregate data they see about the way white people treat
them. And Eugene Prair. And the struggle of the Palestinian people for freedom, for self-determination
and dignity speaks to the exact opposite agenda of the agenda of the imperialists. It speaks
to a crossroads of the world, a cradle of civilization, a West Asia and North Africa rooted in peace,
rooted in people living together regardless of whatever your religion may be, rooted in a democratic
set of values. I mean, it's the exact opposite of the brutal, corrupt regimes that have been installed
with Israel at the center.
So these are events that you can attend. It's $10 to come in person and $5 to watch on live stream.
And all folks under 18 are free admission. Just go to peoplesforum.org and get your ticket.
And let's just say that you can't do any of this, but you want to support,
go to amandaseals.com and donate because this whole thing is coming out of my pocket.
So excited to finally make this happen. And it's only happening because the Amanda Lander has said,
we want this. We want to be together in person and we want to put our minds together
to elevate not just ourselves, but our community. So we'll be doing that this weekend at the first
ever Amanda Lander Summit. Oh, and before I forget, we're going to have the Amanda Lander export store
pop-up. So for those of you who want to get your goodies and also some exclusive stuff that is not
available online, we will see you at the People's Forum. And yes, we will have security because we are
not playing with these crazy people. Amanda Lander